(Leonard:)He wanted me to find out if you'd have
a problem with him asking her out.
Well, I'm not sure how to respond,
Leonard.
I mean, I don't own Amy.
You can't own a person.
(Sheldon:)At least, not since...
(Sheldon:)1863.
(Sheldon:)President Lincoln freed the...
The slaves. Come on, Leonard,
if you're gonna teach history...
(Sheldon:)...these are the kind of facts
you'll have to know.
(Leonard:)You know what? Never mind.
I'm gonna tell him it's okay to ask her out.
(Sheldon:)The question is moot.
There is no way that Stuart...
(Sheldon:)...an impoverished peddler
of picture books...
(Sheldon:)...would be at all appealing
to Amy Farrah Fowler...
(Sheldon:)...a noted neurobiologist...
(Sheldon:)...capable of performing surgery
on her own feet...
(Sheldon:)...with nothing but nitrous oxide from
cans of whipped cream as anesthesia.
All right, but for the record...